<INTERESTS>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Video Games: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Halo</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A sci-fi first-person shooter game set in a distant future.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Video Games: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Skyrim</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An open-world RPG set in a mythical land filled with dragons.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Video Games: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>The Legend of Zelda</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An open-world action-adventure game where players explore the kingdom of Hyrule.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Video Games: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Bioshock</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A first-person shooter set in the dystopian underwater city of Rapture, where players unravel the mysteries of the city’s downfall while battling genetically modified enemies.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Video Games: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An open-world RPG that follows Geralt of Rivia, a monster hunter, as he searches for his adopted daughter, battling monsters and making morally complex decisions that impact the story.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Hobbies: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Gym</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Engaging in physical exercise, weightlifting, and fitness routines at the gym.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Hobbies: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Hiking</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Exploring trails and mountains, often on weekends for relaxation and adventure.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Hobbies: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Kayaking</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Enjoying water-based activities and paddling through rivers and lakes.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Hobbies: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Traveling</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Visiting new places, experiencing different cultures, and exploring destinations worldwide.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Spider-Man</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Follows the adventures of Peter Parker as he protects New York City as Spider-Man.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>LOTR (Lord of the Rings)</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An epic fantasy tale of hobbits, elves, and men fighting to save Middle-Earth.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Star Wars</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A space-fantasy saga featuring the battle between the Jedi and the Sith.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>007 (James Bond)</NAME>
      <DETAILS>Following the adventures of James Bond, a British spy with a license to kill.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Harry Potter</NAME>
      <DETAILS>The story of a young wizard, Harry Potter, and his battles against dark forces.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>South Park</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An animated sitcom following the lives of four boys in the town of South Park.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Breaking Bad</NAME>
      <DETAILS>The story of a high school chemistry teacher turned meth producer.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Rick and Morty</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An animated sci-fi sitcom about a mad scientist and his adventures with his grandson.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Ed, Edd n Eddy</NAME>
      <DETAILS>An animated show about three friends trying to make money and avoid trouble.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Adventure Time</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A cartoon about Finn the Human and Jake the Dog in the Land of Ooo.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Game of Thrones</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A medieval fantasy series about power struggles in the Seven Kingdoms.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
   <INTEREST>
      <CATEGORY>Movies / Shows: </CATEGORY>
      <NAME>Many more</NAME>
      <DETAILS>A variety of additional shows and movies across multiple genres.</DETAILS>
   </INTEREST>
</INTERESTS>
